what happens while things come very
qué pasa mientras vienen las cosas muy
hot
calentita
but warm I am because we are
pero calentito estoy porque estamos en
live right now ok so that I am
directo ahora mismo ok para que esté
watching this summarized and I just told
viendo esto resumido y acabo de decirle
people please look while
a la gente por favor mira mientras
we do a little bit of time follow me on
hacemos un poquito de tiempo seguirme en
twitter those of you who do not follow me we are
twitter los que no me sigáis estamos
here 1500 people on youtube how
aquí 1500 personas en youtube cuántas
old the 400 and some do not and I just
años los 400 y pico no y me acaban de
followed like 200 or 300 people or 200
seguir como 200 o 300 personas o sea 200
three hundred people who are here and did not
trescientas personas que están aquí y no
follow me look here it is on instagram
me seguían mira aquí está en instagram
here too dot instagram in case
aquí también punto instagram por si
someone does not know that I have instagram
alguien no sabe que tengo instagram
I am a boomer but I have instagram it is that
soy boomer pero tengo instagram es que
she without with you is that you are
ella sin con ustedes es que sois unos
shameless man if we love you the same
sinvergüenzas tío si te queremos igual
damn be like with there were already 300
un [__] sea como con ya había 300
people who whom directly now
personas a quien a quienes directo ahora
you will see when of summary I have done to
tú verás cuando de sumario he hecho a
youtube another thousand will follow me and I am freaking out
youtube me seguirán otras mil y yo lo
either because you did not follow me ais
flipo sea porque no me seguí ais
javi it ​​is that no
javi es que no
please please well let's see the thing
por favor por favor bueno a ver la cosa
is that the issue of the the issue of
es que el tema de la el tema de
instagram has come because  I
instagram ha venido porque yo en
don't upload many photos on Instagram during the day
instagram por día no subo muchas fotos
because I don't go out
porque porque no salgo
basically it's what you do as soon as
básicamente es que ya haces en cuanto
the corners of the house but continue
por los rincones de la casa pero sigue
your story and I start talking to
su historia y me pongo a hablar con
you the story so I've
ustedes la historia entonces
been uploading today at dawn if you
he estado subiendo hoy de madrugada si
had followed me on Instagram in time you'll
me hubiera seguido en instagram a tiempo
find out about these things first
estas cosas os enteraréis lo primero
but they are coming in almost 24 hours
pero están entrando casi 24 horas
later today on star and I have uploaded a
después hoy en star and he subido un
spoiler of what is being the fight
spoiler de lo que viene siendo la pelea
the fight no, I received some
la bronca no que me llegaron unas
images but they were images okay
imágenes pero eran imágenes vale esto lo
people have been able to enjoy this today the
ha podido disfrutar la gente hoy la
people who already followed me on Instagram those of you who do
gente que me seguía ya en instagram los
n't follow me well you know how to eat
que no me seguís pues sabéis comer los
snot okay so don't be don't be an
mocos vale así que no seáis no seáis
[ __ ] and follow me now everyone
[__] y seguirme ya todo el mundo
on Instagram to see what happens
en instagram para ver qué es lo que pasa
now I have the video they
que ahora tengo el vídeo
sent it to me to try I have not been
me lo han mandado a tratar de no he
able to connect through the new
podido conectar mediante el nuevo
member welcome welcome nano wii
miembro bienvenido bienvenido nano wii
haina didn't come but funny hey do
haina no viniera pero gracia oye hacer
the members you know we have the
los miembros you know tenemos los
members of me new also very to get in
miembros de yo nuevo también muy para
we have abandoned
meter hemos abandonado día
definitive day and I'm definitely leaving he's not
definitivo y definitivamente me voy no
coming to record this [ __ ] here he
viene a grabar esta [__] aquí le
cares that he  they have hit ops already the
importa que se hayan pegado de ops ya la
mother age of life
madre edad de la vida
I'm going to the town if I continue like this I'm going to
me voy al pueblo yo si sigo así me voy
the town soon ham ham ham with the [ __ ] game is called ham ham u s but only ham u s with more youtubers okay with more my mother the youtubers that are on the list listen to me that I'm putting Garcia because the other votes bad photo pipa things follow me on instagram you will
las cosas seguirme en instagram os
find out about everything before all the
enteraréis de todo antes que toda la
people with which later he would find out
gente con el que luego se enterase a los
three days later on his brother's channel or
tres días en el canal del su hermano oa
a week later on Craig Harvey
la semana en el canal de craig harvey
Oliveira's channel the exclusives are here I have
oliveira las exclusivas son aquí tengo
the [ __ ] video I have the point video of the
el [__] vídeo tengo el punto vídeo de la
mother of Dallas pulling her
madre de dallas pegándose tirones de
hair with life to air that 2020 is missing that
pelo con la vida to air que le falta el
2020 is missing please he's
que le falta el 2020 por favor
not missing anything he's
no le falta nada
let's watch the video I have it it's from this
vamos a ver el vídeo lo tengo es de esta
afternoon I have it since this afternoon but I've
tarde lo tengo desde esta tarde pero he
been busy editing the video done I
estado liado editando el vídeo hecho
was busy with other things at
estaba ocupado con otras cosas en la
home and I was editing the video in
casa y estaba editando el vídeo a
bits and pieces  that when
cachitos y con rollo ese cuándo
and when I was able to finish it well then I
y cuando he podido terminarlo pues
uploaded the video and it
entonces después he subido el vídeo y ha
started live when I could
empezado directo cuando he podido
I would have liked to do live streams
me hubiera gustado hoy hacer directos a
early today so you could have the video
temprana para que tuvierais el vídeo
earlier but oh well for that they will process
antes pero bueno para eso tramitarán
okay the
vale
video is very strong the video is very
el vídeo muy fuerte el vídeo es muy
strong
fuerte
the video is very strong
el vídeo muy fuerte
let's watch it slowly because I
vamos a ir viéndolo despacito porque yo
think we have to enjoy it frame by
creo que hay que disfrutarlo fotograma a
frame okay
fotograma vale
here it seems like they're going to eat each other's mouths
aquí parece que se van a comer la boca
hello what's going on [ __ ] a kiss no
hola que pasa [__] un besito no
heads or better yet you missed the nose well
cabezas o mejor te faltó la nariz bueno
we'll see and then they continue over here
ya veremos y luego siguen por aquí
and she snuck in the cutest dye
y se coló de tinte más mono tiene
Sabrina has it listen to me she has very
sabrina escúchame tiene el pelito muy
soft hair it gives you two points of what it's
suave te aporta dos puntos de lo que
made of
está hecho
is that life has it but things and
es que la vida tiene pero las cosas y
now they are like this as they are breaking up
ahora están así como se están partiendo
to hell a bit of a joke made
al [__] un poco de un cachondeo hecho
this the the whatever this is the one from the
este el el como sea éste es el del
video clip the criticize and this whatever his
videoclip el critican y éste como se
name is is here in the back okay he's here in the
llame está aquí atrás valen está aquí
back with a necklace here made of a kilo of
atrás con un collar aquí de un kilo de
melons
melones
with a necklace here made of a kilo of melons
con un collar aquí de un kilo de melones
okay and he's there he's calm watching it
vale y está ahí está tranquilo viéndolo
the bastard me  is recording something and nothing
el cabrón me está grabando algo y nada
here they hug each other it's not that I love you my
aquí se abrazan no es que te quiero mi
sister that I love you there I have a motorcycle the
hermana que te quiero ahí tengo moto el
voice and welcome and then we'll see
voz y acogida y luego vamos a ver para
what happens
qué pasa
and this one comes for her I'll bring her says life
y ésta viene por la traeré dice la vida
but your moment that I have with the whole damn
pero tu momento que tengo con toda la
thing and it's realizing that it's not
cosa [__] y nos está dando cuenta que no
the moment to tell her that I don't know if
es el momento para contarle eso no sé si
at least they are fighting with the
por lo menos están peleando con la
mask
mascarilla
well here we go to that one for
bueno aquí vamos a ese para
a moment there comes not
llega un momento ahí no
in the instagram photos they could be seen let's see
en las fotos de instagram se veían a ver
yes yes let's see people we have to hit each other
sí sí a ver la gente hay que pegarse
but with safety above all okay taking
pero con seguridad ante todo vale
care taking care of your health let's see I don't know
cuidando cuidando la salud a ver no sé
if you're going to get to see it here in the photo
si vais a llegar a verlo aquí en la foto
that upload is great you can see it but I don't
que subir esta gran podéis verlo pero no
know why life takes us pants
sé por qué la vida nos lleva pantalones
and only wears a t-shirt and some
y solamente lleva una camiseta y unas
work boots
botas de trabajo
these boots I wore when I was a
estas botas yo me las ponía cuando era
forklift driver when I was a forklift driver I
carretillero cuando era carretillero me
had to wear this with the
tenía que poner esto con la puntera de
iron toe in case the forklift hit me
hierro por si me pasaba la carretilla
in a clumsy place okay let's watch the
por lugar torpe vale vamos a ver el
video now
vídeo ahora
and that's it
e
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music] I
[Música]
don't know if there was more after it was done
no sé si había más después de hecho
because life is crazy and it gets
porque lo loco es la vida y se pone
ice on the head and it becomes
hielo en la cabeza y se pone a ser
history saying that she has a gap they do
historia diciendo que tiene una brecha
n't do eating the head so I don't
no hacen comiendo la cabeza entonces no
know if there is something going on out there that we have
sé si es que habrá algo va por ahí que
n't lost but here in this
no hayamos perdido pero aquí en esta
account that they just sent me okay here
cuenta que me acaban de mandar vale aquí
in this account that they just sent me
en esta cuenta que me acaban de mandar
jharjand music club de fa there is a
jharjand music club de fa hay una
very interesting story okay
historia muy interesante vale
the gap let's see the gap the gap has been
la brecha a ver la brecha la brecha se
made she made it when she was a girl
ha hecho se la hizo cuando chica
the gap was made when she was a girl anna
la brecha se la hizo cuando chica anna
life but look it will be good for her if she
la vida pero mira le va a venir bien si
has a gap because that way she can give birth
tiene una brecha porque así puede parir
the mask is falling off I
se está caído la careta
'm already fed up and the time has come
ya estoy harta y ha llegado el momento
to tell you the whole truth and everything that
de contaros toda la verdad y todo lo que
has happened in the following stories I am
ha pasado en las siguientes historias os
going to show you how that scoundrel of
voy a enseñar cómo la sinvergüenza de
that lady
esa señora
who tries to make me bald pounces
que intenta dejar calva se abalanza
on me and I am not going to allow it is that I am
sobre mí y no le voy a permitir es que
not going to allow it she is a scoundrel
no lo voy a permitir es una sinvergüenza
and claver all the truth the following
y claver toda la verdad las siguientes
stories of how that scoundrel who
historias de cómo esa sinvergüenza que
tries to make me bald by grabbing me by the
intenta dejar calva cogiéndome de los
hair and I am not going to keep quiet anymore and I am going to
pelos y yo ya no me voy a callar y voy a
spill the whole truth I was silent for a long
soltar toda la verdad ya estaba mucho
time and now yes  truly from the
tiempo callado y ahora sí de verdad de
heart I'm going to put the following
corazón voy a poner las siguientes
stories the truth
historias la verdad
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and
e
gals that longer videos and the
gallas a que vídeos más largos y el
longest video you
vídeo más largo
can see perfectly how life begins
se ve perfectamente cómo empieza la vida
don't catch me you can't see that they have
a mí no me coja no se ve que se han
grabbed each other before
agarrado antes
and the one from Uber and bringing the hamburger
y el del ubera y trayendo la hamburguesa
and life and without pants
y la vida y sin pantalones
because the whole truth
porque toda la verdad
here what we really don't have to
aquí lo que realmente no tenemos que
ask very seriously okay here what we
preguntar muy seriamente vale aquí lo
have to ask ourselves very
que nos tenemos que preguntar muy
seriously
seriamente
why they are because they are in a place
por qué están porque están en un local
that has a gas station in the
que tiene una gasolinera en el
window
escaparate
here outside is a gas station with
aquí afuera es una gasolinera con
windows I
escaparates
mean you have to get inside this
o sea te tienes que meter dentro está
gasoline or you buy it if that were
gasolina o tú la compramos si fuera eso
El Corte Inglés and here they grab each other
el corte inglés y aquí se agarran
e e e e
e
what do you think life begins do
qué cree usted que empieza la vida
n't catch me you can't
a mí no me coja
see you can't see you can't
no se ve no se ve
they are already hooked on the camera life
están ya enganchados a la cámara vida
over there the camera when it comes back it
para allá la cámara cuando vuelve
hooks
engancha
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and she is silent
y ella haya callado
life begins
empieza la vida
and there you can see how this lady is already
y ahí se ve cómo es esta señora ya
estevez the values ​​that she has and there you can
estévez los valores que tiene y ahí se
see how bad a person she is that is something
ve como es de mala persona que es algo
to eat I am so calm with a bunch
de comer yo tan tranquila con un montón
of influencers and she waits for me  at the door of the
de influencers y me espera a la puerta
rest a lot of flowers
del resto montón de flores
the truth was already a lot of check
la verdad ya estaba mucho cheque
character and now yes, truly from the
personaje y ahora sí de verdad de
heart I'm going to put in the following
corazón voy a poner en las siguientes
stories the truth
historias la verdad
look at the pile of influences
mira el montón de influencias
Panama
panamá
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
the volume doesn't go up not even from the motorcycle
el volumen no se levanta ni de la moto
second life to the mother of Dallas
segunda vida a la madre de dallas la
looked at her badly and this that he couldn't the
miraba mal y esto que no podía el the
lover counts as influence of
lover cuenta como influencia de
influence influence the uber account
influencia influencia la cuenta de uber
has many followers and there you see how
tiene muchos seguidores y ahí se ve como
this lady is now he sees the values
es esta señora ya éste ve los valores
that she has and there you see how she is of a bad
que tiene y ahí se ve como es de mala
person that is something to eat me so
persona que es algo de comer yo tan
calm with a bunch of influencers
tranquila con un montón de influencers
waiting at the door of the restaurant
en espera a la puerta del restaurante
to grab me by the hair well it's not
para cogerme de los pelos pues no se
fallen the mask is falling without
está caído se está caído la careta sin
shame
vergüenza
yes yes yes the mother true that yes
sí sí sí la madre verdad que sí
and they would wish I bet something
y desearían apuesto algo
and
e
[Music]
[Música]
and life is how it goes let's go with the next one
y la vida como va vamos con la siguiente
I'm freaking out because all these are people who did
yo flipo porque todo esto son gente que
n't follow me let's go I'm freaking out let's see
no me seguían vamos estoy flipando a ver
life like
la vida como
[Music]
[Música]
like what followers
como vaya seguidores
here is the lock
aquí está el candado
but this is not
pero ésta no es
this account is not
esta cuenta no es
[Music]
[Música]
and there it is known that it is not given
y ahí se sepa que no se da
the real life the web life
de la vida de verdad la vida
and what is the real one it's
y cuál es la de verdad
not that it wasn't called life your in the
no es que no se llamaba la vida tu en la
account it's not the one that comes out with a crown
cuenta no es la que sale con una corona
at the end where those people this thing about 2
al final donde esa gente esto lo del 2
in red but here it was yesterday I can't
en tinto pero aquí era ayer no me puedo
eat it
comer
a video of the year will fall I think
le va a caer un vídeo del año creo
this totally paints a video of Dallas
esto pinta totalmente vídeo de dallas
subscribe subscribe
suscribiros
subscribe to javier canino
suscribiros suscribiros a javier canino
and oliveira because any move I
y oliveira porque cualquier movida le
'm giving it in the minute okay any
estoy dando en el minuto vale cualquier
move I'm giving it in the minute
movida la estoy dando en el minuto
subscribe everyone
suscribiros todo el mundo
what is what would the account
cuál es cuál sería la cuenta
nobody knows
nadie lo sabe
this
esto
in tones I will not enter the computer I don't know
en tonos no entraré del ordenador no sé
why
por qué
very bad Dallas' mom does not mistreat herself
muy mal la mamá de dallas no se maltrata
if a pregnant woman
si a una embarazada
I am very bastards in the comments of the
soy muy cabrones en los comentarios del
previous video I am very bastards this
vídeo anterior soy muy cabrones esta
comic that if gender violence
historieta de que si violencia de género
that if I don't know what well well we don't give a damn I
que si no sé qué
wanted to see I wanted to want to
bueno pues nos la suda quería ver quería
see how many followers I had
quería ver cuántos seguidores había
gained with this move but well the
ganado con esta movida pero bueno lo
important thing is that they do it so
importante es que lo hagan ellos así que
everyone please follow me on my
todo el mundo por favor seguirme en mi
instagram account because in a minute you are
cuenta de instagram porque al minuto os
studying all the information there and
estudiando toda la información ahí y
here in the channels I sit at the
aquí en los canales me siento en
computer very  pompom video instantly
ordenador muy pompón vídeo al instante
always worth it always here you have my
siempre vale siempre aquí tenéis mi
instagram I
instagram
made it promote because here efe
la he hecho la promover porque acá efe
[ __ ] is thrown at dallas here you have
se le tira [__] a dallas aquí tenéis
my twitter
mi twitter
in the middle
en medio
a video has reached a million
un vídeo ha llegado un millón de
followers urged the chick
seguidores instaron la tipa
seriously
en serio
Victor yes but I think she had them or
víctor sí pero yo creo que los tenía o
she was close or something like that
le faltaba poco o algo así
and well tomorrow we will see tomorrow we will see what
y bueno mañana veremos mañana veremos
happens with this
que lo que pasa con esto